

PROFILE

I am a software developer with two years of experience in mobile and web development. I have extensive knowledge of several programming languages, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Python, and Kotlin. I also have a strong understanding of system design, user interface design, and various system architectures in the software development cycle.

CONTACT

PHONE: 0720 012 365

WEBSITE:

https://cyrusgm.netlify.app/

EMAIL:

cyrusgitau08@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Coding Tech Research Reading Novels Swimming

CYRUS.M. GITAU

Software Engineer

EDUCATION

Muranga University of Technology

2016 - 2021

I got a Second-Class Honors in Bachelor Of Business Information Technology

Mururia High School

2011 - 2015

I Got a B Plain of 64 Points in my Kenya Certificate Of Secondary Education (K.C.S.E)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Muva Developers (Cross-Platform Developer)

October 2022-Current

My primary role is to design and develop cross platform applications that work in android an IOS platforms

Freelance Work (Software developer)

Jan 2021–September 2022

I designed and developed various websites and applications for clients in freelancing sites like fiverr, Upwork and Turing

Simba Technology Limited (Intern Developer)

May 2019-Aug 2019

I worked on various projects with other developers and learnt the various aspects of the software development Lifecycle

SKILLS

